{"data":[{"question":"Please answer the questions _____ page 26","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner,at the bus stop,at the door,at the top of the page,at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"2"},{"question":"The driver became very nervous _____ the police checkpoint","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner,at the bus stop,at the door,at the top of the page,at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"2"},{"question":"Mr. Norton is a partner ____ a prestigious New York law firm","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner,at the bus stop,at the door,at the top of the page,at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"2"},{"question":"You'll have to excuse me. I'm going to grab a cup of coffee _____ Starbucks before work.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner,at the bus stop,at the door,at the top of the page,at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"2"},{"question":"The situation has been better _____ the telecommunications industry.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":" Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"2"},{"question":"The same data can be found _____ different servers","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":" Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"2"},{"question":"There is no water _____ that island","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":" Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"2"},{"question":"How many people work ___ that advertising agency?","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":" Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"2"},{"question":"Norma has invested quite a bit of money _____ the stock market recently.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"2"},{"question":"Mark is studying law _____ Harvard.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":" Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"2"}]}